You
Wait a minute is is this even the right place this hotel is huge
Kiriyama Nikaido
Mr. Shimada's being interviewed in the waiting room. It's the 20th anniversary, and there's also a fan gathering happening today
He's got to be tired and the matches start tomorrow
The fan gatherings beginning at 3 see if you can find mr. Shimada in there and try to stick close to him
Wait, are you sure about this? We don't have anything to do with it. Won't it be weird?
Nothing to do with it. What are you talking about? We're in the same workshop
And I'm his pupil when he's surrounded by all those strangers and has to remain calm
I'll be there to make sure he doesn't get worn out the day before his first match
It'll probably be a relief for him to see a familiar face
He's more sensitive to that kind of thing than most people
What is it never mind it's nothing really I understand
Nikaido, I feel like you're more mature than me now
Besides
It's good to experience this kind of environment and start getting used to it
So when the time comes no matter what I'll be able to maintain my focus
Huh, when what comes I'll need these skills when it's my turn to play in the title match of course
What the hell? How can you be so sure? It's not like you know what's gonna happen
We're still just C1 and C2 right now
It'll come
I'll get my shot at the title. You'll see I'll make it happen. I have to believe it. How else can I go on?
Nikaido
I felt the determination as he spoke and a chill suddenly ran up my spine
Hey, Ray
Well, see you back at the hall around three, okay? Yeah, okay
I've been spending all my time overthinking
While Nikaido has been sharpening his resolve
There's something I've been meaning to talk to you about
So, uh, about your prize money and match earnings
Most of it's been deposited into my bank account
And I know what you've been trying to do
You're trying to pay me back for taking you in
I'm grateful, but there's no need for that
Yeah, but I can't let you do that forever
Don't worry about it, Coda
You go ahead and hang on to the kid's money
If he suddenly ran into a small fortune
Who knows what scandalous things he'd blow it on
Chairman, Ray isn't that kind of boy
I see
And come to think of it, even if he wanted to
There isn't anything shady that a boy his age could blow money on
How unfortunate
He's got all this money, but not a single thing to spend it on
Hey, how about a woman?
Could you at the very least support a selfish girlfriend?
You're still an eligible bachelor, right, little Kiwiwama, right?
That really hurts
Chairman, please, leave us alone
Well, like the chairman said, I'll hold on to your money for now until you come of age
But let me know if you need it
Ah, right
How's Kyoko been doing lately?
I hear she often stays at your place
Is that a hassle for you?
Huh?
What is he talking about?
So she's not with you?
Thought so
I don't know what to do
I just have no idea what she's thinking anymore
Father
Kyoko's been
Kota 8th done
Kyriyama 5th done
Excuse me, can I get some shots of you two?
What do I do?
Should I tell him?
But
If he finds out, he'll
What's going to happen to her?
Is there
Anything that I can do about it right now?
This garden is amazing
I can't believe a hotel in the city actually has a place like this
How nice
I wonder why they always keep passing each other by
Neither father
Nor Kyoko really want to break off their relationship entirely
A sun shower
So yeah
Hey
Ah, there you are
Hey So yeah
You numbskull
This is your time to shine
I was wondering where you went off to
Then just look at you
You're soaking wet
Kiriyama
You were standing right next to him and didn't bring him in
Let's get going
You too
Right
Sorry about that
What are you doing staring at a pond in the rain
When the main event's inside?
That was a surprise
As usual
There was no warning
The moment I laid eyes on him
The entire world went silent
Wow, he hasn't changed a bit
He looks the same as when he was a teenager
I remember someone saying
He isn't human
The moment he left
The sky broke open
And heavy rain began to pour
He's going up against that man
Mr. Shimada
It was a pretty strange sight
When he entered the hall
The whole room went silent
And the crowd parted for him
Sorry about that, everyone
Thanks for your patience
It turns out he was in the garden
Just watching the koi swim around
This guy's going to be the death of me, right?
Well, let's get started
Come on, Soya, you're up
At age 15
He became a professional
At 21
He was the youngest Shogi Grandmaster in history
From there
He went on to break one record after another
Which included winning all seven major Shogi titles
But that was over 10 years ago
He's remained the champion ever since
And he still looks exactly the same
Without diminishing, tiring, or ever dishonoring the game
With that overwhelming power
He continues to reign supreme
Hey there
It's been a while
Some say he could be compared to a god
But I've also heard people say
That if
If he were to see the devil
He'd have the same expression
Now let's continue with Shimada e ten
If you would
Good evening, everyone
I'd like to thank you all for being here
Especially those of you who have traveled far to join us
Thank you for coming
About three weeks have passed since I became the challenger
Just when the party was about to end
Mr. Shimada said
Twice
Somehow I have to find a way to beat that monster twice
Otherwise I'll never get there
To the sixth match
It's in my hometown
Kai Shimada
Eighth den
In a seven-match showdown
After 114 moves
He conceded
Hey, Ray
What do you want from me?
You snitched on me to dad, didn't you?
Like I said in the text I sent
I didn't tell him anything
He put a stop on my card
And he won't leave me alone with all these questions
What am I supposed to do now?
This is all your fault
I just told you I didn't tell him anything
The truth is
You brought this on yourself
And you know it
I brought it on myself?
Excuse me?
Who the hell do you think you are?
Are you kidding me?
All you do is whine and suck at playing shogi
That's got nothing to do with it
What the hell are you saying?
Wait
Oh, Momo
Ray, who are they?
Kari
Oh, hi
Sorry for interrupting
Please, don't mind us
You're fighting
You're fighting?
Why me?
Come on
Let's go
Why is she being me to Ray Ray?
It'll be fine
Okay
I feel bad
Guess he was in the middle of something serious
Scary
Is she a witch?
Don't worry, Momo
Let's just go home and enjoy our Inari Sushi
What?
Well, from the looks of it
Ray is dealing with a strong-willed girl
Those girls
Who are they to you?
They're my neighbors
They've done a lot for me since I moved
So that's the next home, huh?
I bet you put on the whole
Woe is me act for them
Are they taking good care of you?
Trying to screw up another family?
You're a piece of work
What is this?
I can't believe my heart's beating so fast
I've never seen Ray's face so pale before
We've never seen him look like that
On top of that
He didn't even see us
He never looked our way
You have to eat these, Ray
Akari and I made them
They're full of egg and sesame seeds
They're sweet and they're really delicious
They're gonna cheer you up
So you better eat them
Thanks, Ina
Come on
We're done here
What is her problem, anyway?
She is bad news
I just knew it
Alright, Hina
Calm down
It's okay
No need to get so worked up
This is scary, which kind
What is wrong with Ray, anyway?
Why'd he just stand there and take it?
I know
I have to admit
I agree with you
A little
I know, right?
But
Just a little
This is what they made for you?
It's too sweet
It almost tastes like candy
But this one
It has minced pickled wasabi in it
Oh no, I can't stop eating them
They all taste so good
I better not make me sad
What do you expect me to do about that?
You follow me home, eat my food, which was a gift, and complain?
Really?
There's even vegetables with simmered chicken and lotus root
They're like old ladies
A little cliche, don't you think?
I'm the perfect housewife
How ridiculous
This is just what a growing boy needs to grow up healthy and strong
What a joke
Meh
Ooh, there's broccoli in there
Ooh, yum
Boiled with sesame oil and sea salt?
Korean style
Hmm
Crunch, crunch, crunch
Munch, munch
Lick
Alright, you'd better start heading home
They'll be expecting you for dinner
But I can't move
My skirt is too tight
I feel miserable
What?
I'm so stuffed
I'm getting a full-on food coma
Let me borrow a sweatshirt or something for the night
I'm staying here
Don't be ridiculous
Father's already mad
Just go home
Please, shut up already
I'll call him later, alright?
Hey, what are you doing?
I never said you could look in there
Toss, toss, toss!
Swooch!
Knock it off!
I finally feel better
Hey, which girl?
What's that?
Is it that middle schooler?
Wait, don't tell me
It's not that housewife, is it?
Hold on
What are you talking about?
Housewife?
Wait, do you mean Akari?
So her name's Akari
Not that I really care
She was the one holding her little sister
Huh?
Yeah, those three girls are sisters
Actually
I don't think Akari
I don't think Akari's really that much older than you
Huh?
There's no way!
Then, which one?
The one in middle school?
Or the older sister?
Come on, are you serious?
Why even say something like that?
It's neither of them
What do you expect?
Seriously?
Wait, not the kindergartner?
What a perfect!
You, just go home already!
I already told you
I'm at Ray's place, okay?
You don't have a problem with me being here, do you?
Easy for you to say
The last train is long gone now
Ray
What is his problem?
Why doesn't he trust his own daughter?
I don't understand Yoko anymore
Yeah, I feel the same
I know exactly where you're coming from
Yoko
What are you gonna do now?
He's really worried about you
Not my problem
There's always something with him
He said if I have a boyfriend that's taking care of me
He wants to meet him
So bring him over
Yeah, right
The guy's 20 years older than me and he's married
And on top of that, dad used to be his shogi coach
There's no way I could bring him home
Why would you even go for a guy like that?
I don't know, Ray
I keep asking myself the same thing
That little girl
She called me
A witch
If I really was a witch
I wouldn't be in such pathetic shape
Hey, Ray
What do you think I should do?
I'm scared
In the darkness of the night
All I could do was lie there and watch
Over
And over
And over again
The glow from her cell phone
Let up her silhouette
The entire room
Felt like it was filled with blue light
As if we were at the bottom of the sea together
It felt like all we did that night
Was sink deeper
When she said she'd see me later
I started to say yeah
But I couldn't get the words out
Ever since then
Even though I felt torn when I left that house
Nothing's changed
Because
We're still stuck in the same place
Then
And even now
Kyoko and I
Are neither siblings
Nor strangers
Hi
Sorry for being late
Hey, no problem
Wait
Did you run here?
Sorry
I was on cleaning duty
And it ran long
Cleaning duty?
Oh
Haven't heard that in a while
That brings back some memories
I see
You really are still just a student, aren't you?
Come inside already
Nikaido's been impatiently waiting for you to finally get here
Hey
There you are, finally
I won the final match
In the next term
I'll be C1 same as you
Keep your voice down, will ya?
That sound and your attitude annoy the hell out of me
Shigeta
Congratulations on successfully keeping your rank
It was up in the air for a while
I thought there was a chance
You might even be in danger of coming back down to my class
Are you kidding?
What are you talking about?
What match were you watching?
I didn't have to go all out once this season
You both did great
Just be glad no one got any bad news
I managed to hold on to my A-class rank this season too
To be honest with ya
I basically just squeaked by
I was right on the border
And managed to make it by a hair
Make it by a hair?
When he says that, it really makes sense
Congratulations, sincerely
What's wrong?
Why are you guys all crying?
I finally caught up to you, Kiriyama
I'm looking forward to a squaring off
It's gonna be epic
Since we're rivals
Yeah, that's right
When Nikaido spoke
He lit up so brightly it was blinding
It reminded me of the sunshine on the river's surface
I'll be turning 18 next month
It'll be my second year in high school
Nothing will have changed at all
And yet
A new spring will begin again
Inve OFF
In approach
Distinguished
For a while
you've definitely знаем
If youre
That raus
in your life
You're
physician
instant
You're
you're
Your
really
You may
you
You're
I was wondering if you might be free tomorrow afternoon?
Then how about going to Mouse Land?
The two of us!
Let me think about it.
How can I put this?
It just feels like it's unsettling.
Don't miss the next March Comes In Like a Lion!
Kiriyama, our fierce battle is just beginning!
Rival vs. Rival!